mudah.my 2019-06-17

# About Mudah - Mudah.my

Mudah.my.Sdn. Bhd. (" **Mudah** ") is committed to protecting your personal information and will take the relevant measures to safeguard your personal information in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Act 2010 and Personal Data Protection Regulations 2013 including their revisions. This Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") sets out how we use and protect the information you give us.

This Privacy Policy supplements our Terms & Conditions of Use and explains how we handle the information collected and received when you visit our website Mudah.my, our official Android or iOS apps and all the related sub-sites (" **Site** "). It also governs the collection, use and disclosure of your information.

## Collection of Personal Information

We may collect information that personally identifies you if you choose to submit your personal information for the various purposes made available on our Site for example, when you visit or browse our website, register or subscribe to be our Users, used our Products and/or Services, participate in any of our surveys, promotions or marketing campaigns etc.

Personal information includes any information which relates directly or indirectly to you, which can be used to identify or contact you.

When you visit the Site through your computer, mobile device, or any other device with internet connectivity, Mudah servers will automatically record data that your browser sends for examples your IP address and information about your visit (such as time stamp, date, duration etc).

We may use cookies (small text files placed in the memory of your browser or device when you visit the Site) that will allow us to recognize a particular device or browser and help us personalise the content to match your preferred interests more quickly, and to make our Services and Site more convenient and useful to you. You may be able to manage and delete cookies through your browser or device settings. For more information on how to do so, visit the help material of your browser or device.

Any information we collect from the User may be used but not limited to any of the following ways: -

  * To verify the identity of the User
  * To personalise your experience on our Site
  * To improve our Site and services provided to you
  * To process any transactions
  * To send periodical emails on information and updates on the Site, related product or service information
  * To identify visitors on the Platform
  * To detect and prevent fraudulent activity
  * To conduct marketing research activities
  * To comply with applicable Anti-Money Laundering and Countering the Financing of Terrorism regulations and other applicable laws and regulations

In addition to other information described in this Privacy Policy, we may collect and share with third party data management platforms or advertising and analytics partners precise location information. This location information may be used by itself, aggregated, or combined with mobile identifiers (such as IDFAs and Android IDs), and shared with third parties for purposes related to advertising, analytics, attribution (e.g., measuring ad performance), analytics and market research.

The processing of your personal information will be done in accordance with all applicable laws. In processing your personal information, we shall take practical and reasonable steps to protect the personal information from any loss, misuse, modification, unauthorized or accidental disclosure, alteration or destruction.

The User shall be deemed to have consented to the collection, use and disclosure of personal data of relevant individuals by the User’s continued dealing and usage of the Services on the Site.

Please take note that if at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, please follow the instructions to unsubscribe at the bottom of each email.

## Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Mudah may disclose your personal information to the following parties (including those outside Malaysia) for the purposes stated below:

  * agents and service providers who provide services relating to the purposes of which the personal information is collected including data processing services;
  * any person, who is under a duty of confidentiality who has undertaken the responsibility to keep such information confidential; and
  * Mudah's related and associate companies and affiliates.

However, we may disclose your personal information if required by law or in good faith, if such action is necessary to comply with any law enforcement agency requirements, court orders or legal processes.

We may disclose data and aggregate statistics about users of our Services and sales to prospective partners, advertisers, sponsors and other reputable third parties in order to describe our Services, deliver targeted advertisements or for other lawful purposes, but these data and statistics will not include information which can be used to identify you.

## Access and Update of Your Personal Information

If you would like to access, update, correct or delete your personal information, you may contact us at dpo@mudah.my. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request to access, update or correct your personal information within 21 days of receiving your request and such request may be subject to a fee and will be bound by data protection laws in Malaysia.

## Changes to this Policy

Mudah may review and change this Policy from time to time to reflect changes in the law, our business practices, processes or structure. While it is not generally feasible to notify you of the changes to this Policy, the latest version of this Policy will be available on our website. This policy is not a contract, nor does it suggest any obligation on our part with another party.
